And the red sky drifts down a winding
road.
الانزياح الأحمر والسماء الحمراء تنساب على
درب ملتوي.
As the evening shifts in an endless snow.
والمساء يتحول في ثلج لا ينتهي.
Beneath fiery red, there's a big black
gate.
تحت الأحمر المشتعل بوابة سوداء كبيرة.
In a town that's dead at the end of the
straight.
في بلدة ميتة في آخر الطريق.
Upon entrance here in the center square.
عند الدخول هنا في الساحة.
There's a sense of fear.
There's a well that's bare.
حس بالخوف وبئر فارغة.
And the well goes deep.
With a look below.
والبئر تعمق انظر إلى القاع.
And its sides are steep.
There's a faint white glow.
وجدرانها سحيقة توهج أبيض خافت.
To the faint white glow.
For this town that's dead, all the pain
does flow as the well runs red.
إلى التوهج الأبيض الخافت لهذه البلدة
الميتة يسيل كل الألم والبئر تجري حمراء.